So we started
Worship Music and
Arts Club,
formerly PSU
Worship, to give
students a space
to worship God
and to invite
others in to the
beauty and joy of
who He is.
Next semester,
we're talking
with artists like
Pat Barrett and
Caleb King about
coming here to
our campus to
worship together,
encourage each
other, and just
build up the body
of Christ here at
Penn State.
Our student band
of Gentle and
Lowly is about to
release our first
three-song EP.
It's fully
written and
recorded by
students here.
And we plan to
continue to
write, record,
and release music
together in the
following
semesters.
Man, God is just
doing so much
here
through music.
And if you're a
student here and
want to be a part
of that, we'd
encourage you to
think and pray
about becoming
involved in
Worship Music and Arts Club.
We have a
leadership and
team application
at the end of
this video.
We've just been
so encouraged by
what God is doing
here at
Penn State.
And we know that
He doesn't need
us, but He wants
us to be a part
of what
He's doing.
So let's all just
lean into that
together and just
continue to bring
all the
glory to Jesus.